Guide to the Pierce County Central Labor Council Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Pierce County Central Labor Council records
1890-1989
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
2882
Pierce County Central Labor Council (Wash.)
37.34 cubic feet
Local coordinating arm of AFL-CIO
The Tacoma Trades Council was organized in 1890 as an independent organization. It was dormant March, 1895 until November, 1899 when it affiliated with the American Federation of Labor. After it was dissolved in September, 1907, a new body, the Tacoma Central Labor Council, was chartered by the AFL in November, 1907. The records of the Tacoma Trades Council were turned over to the Central Labor council at this time. As a result of the AFL-CIO merger the Tacoma Central Labor Council (AFL) and the Pierce County Industrial Union Council (CIO) merged to form the Pierce County Central Labor Council in December, 1957. In 1909 the Central Labor Council established its newspaper, the "Tacoma Labor Advocate," which was published until 1978.
Organized into 4 accessions.
Accession No. 2882-001, Pierce County Central Labor Council records, 1890-1970
Accession No. 2882-002, Pierce County Central Labor Council interview, 1978-1979
Accession No. 2882-003, Pierce County Central Labor Council meeting minutes, 1890-1926
Accession No. 2882-004, Pierce County Central Labor Council records, 1942-1989
Consult the scope and content information for each of the accessions listed below.
Consult the access restrictions information for each of the accessions listed below.
Bates Technical College; Labor Temple Corporation; Pierce County Central Labor Council (Wash.)$vArchives; Washington (State).$bVocational Training Board.$bApprentice Training Committee; Hupp, Clyde H.$vInterviews; McIlvaigh, Harry S.$vInterviews; Magnuson, Warren G.$q(Warren Grant),$d1905-1989$vCorrespondence; Bone, Homer Truett,$d1883-1970$vCorrespondence; AFL-CIO; Labor Temple Corporation (Tacoma, Wash.); Pierce County Central Labor Council (Wash.).$bPolitician Education Pierce County Committee; Tacoma Central Labor Council.$bLabor Day Committee; Tacoma Central Labor Council.$bMother Robinson Committee; United Labor Advisory Committee (Pierce County, Wash.); Washington State Committee on Apprentice Training; Washington State Apprenticeship Council; Women's Union Card and Label League (Tacoma, Wash.); Pierce County Industrial Union Council (Pierce County, Wash.); Tacoma Central Labor Council; Tacoma Trades Council; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Washington (State)$xPolitics and government$y1889-1950; Washington (State)$xPolitics and government$y1951-; Labor unions$zWashington (State); Labor Day$zWashington (State); Women labor union members$zWashington (State); Apprentices$zWashington (State); American newspapers$zWashington (State); Labor journalism$zWashington (State); Interviews; Transcripts; Resolutions; Audiotapes; Microfilms; Tacoma labor advocate
Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Washington (State); Tacoma; Scrapbooks
- Pierce County Central Labor Council records, 1890-1970; 2882-001; 30.83 cubic feet
  Correspondence (1913-1970); minutes (1890-1967), including those of predecessor organization Tacoma Central Labor Council; financial records; reports; resolutions; conference and convention records; news releases and press files including clippings. Clippings scrapbook subjects include news coverage, leaflets and circulars related to Tacoma labor news, 1935-1946; coverage of Washington State Initiative 130, a 1938 proposal restricting the right to strike; news regarding a proposal for a new Tacoma City Charter (1955-1956); and proposed Washington State initiatives attempting to adopt “right-to-work” laws, I-198 (1956) and I-202 (1958). Subject files include material regarding the 1918 general strike and issues concerning Tacoma-area unions, 1917-1930s.
  Records of related organizations are also included. These include those of the Pierce County Committee on Political Education (COPE) (1958-1972); the Labor Temple Corporation (1918-1959); Labor Advocate Publishing Company (1910-1959); United Labor Advisory Committee of Pierce County, including campaign materials and correspondence related to I-198 and I-202 (1956-1962); the Washington Vocational Training Board Apprentice Training Council (1933-1946); and Tacoma Women’s Union Card and Label League (1915-1925).
  Open to all users, but access to portions of the papers restricted. Contact repository for details.
  Donated by the Council, 7/18/1978.
  - PIERCE COUNTY CENTRAL LABOR COUNCIL, Records Subgroup 1
    - CONSTITUTION AND BYLAWS, 1914; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, Undated, 1914 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - HISTORICAL MATERIALS, Undated; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Historical materials, lists of affiliates, Undated (Box-folder 1/2)
    - CORRESPONDENCE, 1913-1970; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/3-22/3)
      - Incoming Correspondence, 1913-1970; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/3-17/30)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1913 (Box-folder 1/3)
        - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/4)
        - Barbers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/5)
        - Bartenders International League, 1913 (Box-folder 1/6)
        - Boiler Makers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/7)
        - Brewery Workmen of America, 1913 (Box-folder 1/8)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1913 (Box-folder 1/9)
        - Carpenters, 1913 (Box-folder 1/10)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1913 (Box-folder 1/11)
        - Cigarmakers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/12)
        - Cooks and Waiters, 1913 (Box-folder 1/13)
        - C, 1913 (Box-folder 1/14)
        - Electrical Workers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/15)
        - D-F, 1913 (Box-folder 1/16)
        - Garment Workers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/17)
        - Grain Handlers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/18)
        - Hatters, 1913 (Box-folder 1/19)
        - G-H, 1913 (Box-folder 1/20)
        - Laundry Workers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/21)
        - Longshoremen, 1913 (Box-folder 1/22)
        - I-L, 1913 (Box-folder 1/23)
        - Machinists, 1913 (Box-folder 1/24)
        - Mine Workers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/25)
        - M-N, 1913 (Box-folder 1/26)
        - Painters, 1913 (Box-folder 1/27)
        - Plumbers, 1913 (Box-folder 1/28)
        - Printing Pressmen, 1913 (Box-folder 1/29)
        - P, 1913 (Box-folder 1/30)
        - R-S, 1913 (Box-folder 1/31)
        - Teamsters, 1913 (Box-folder 1/32)
        - Typographical Union, 1913 (Box-folder 1/33)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1913 (Box-folder 1/34)
        - T-Z, 1913 (Box-folder 1/35)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1914 (Box-folder 1/36)
        - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/37)
        - Barbers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/38)
        - Bartenders International League, 1914 (Box-folder 1/39)
        - Blacksmiths, 1914 (Box-folder 1/40)
        - Boiler Makers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/41)
        - Brewery Workmen of America, 1914 (Box-folder 1/42)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1914 (Box-folder 1/43)
        - B, 1914 (Box-folder 1/44)
        - Carpenters, 1914 (Box-folder 1/45)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1914 (Box-folder 1/46)
        - Cigarmakers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/47)
        - Cooks and Waiters, 1914 (Box-folder 1/48)
        - C, 1914 (Box-folder 1/49)
        - Electrical Workers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/50)
        - Gas Workers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/51)
        - Iron Workers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/52)
        - Joint Legislative Committee, 1914 (Box-folder 1/53)
        - E-J, 1914 (Box-folder 1/54)
        - Longshoremen, 1914 (Box-folder 1/55)
        - Machinists, 1914 (Box-folder 1/56)
        - Mine Workers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/57)
        - Musicians, 1914 (Box-folder 1/58)
        - K-N, 1914 (Box-folder 1/59)
        - Painters, 1914 (Box-folder 1/60)
        - Plumbers, 1914 (Box-folder 1/61)
        - P, 1914 (Box-folder 1/62)
        - Stage Employees, 1914 (Box-folder 1/63)
        - R-S, 1914 (Box-folder 1/64)
        - Tailors, 1914 (Box-folder 2/1)
        - Teamsters, 1914 (Box-folder 2/2)
        - Theatrical Federation, 1914 (Box-folder 2/3)
        - Typographical Union, 1914 (Box-folder 2/4)
        - T-U, 1914 (Box-folder 2/5)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1914 (Box-folder 2/6)
        - Tacoma Women's Union Card and Label League, 1914 (Box-folder 2/7)
        - W-Z, 1914 (Box-folder 2/8)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1915 (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/10)
        - Barbers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/11)
        - Bartenders, 1915 (Box-folder 2/12)
        - Boiler Makers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/13)
        - Brewery Workmen of America, 1915 (Box-folder 2/14)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1915 (Box-folder 2/15)
        - B, 1915 (Box-folder 2/16)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1915 (Box-folder 2/17)
        - Cigarmakers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/18)
        - Cooks and Waiters, 1915 (Box-folder 2/19)
        - C-D, 1915 (Box-folder 2/20)
        - Electrical Workers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/21)
        - E-F, 1915 (Box-folder 2/22)
        - Garment Workers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/23)
        - Gas Workers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/24)
        - Iron Workers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/25)
        - Longshoremen, 1915 (Box-folder 2/26)
        - G-L, 1915 (Box-folder 2/27)
        - Machinists, 1915 (Box-folder 2/28)
        - Mine Workers, 1915 (Box-folder 2/29)
        - Musicians, 1915 (Box-folder 2/30)
        - M-N, 1915 (Box-folder 2/31)
        - Railway Carmen, 1915 (Box-folder 2/32)
        - Sign and Pictorial Painters, 1915 (Box-folder 2/33)
        - Stage Employees, 1915 (Box-folder 2/34)
        - O-S, 1915 (Box-folder 2/35)
        - Teamsters, 1915 (Box-folder 2/36)
        - Theatrical Federation, 1915 (Box-folder 2/37)
        - Typographical Union, 1915 (Box-folder 2/38)
        - T-U, 1915 (Box-folder 2/39)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1915 (Box-folder 2/40)
        - Tacoma Women's Union Card and Label League, 1915 (Box-folder 2/41)
        - V-Z, 1915 (Box-folder 2/42)
        - A-Z, 1915 (Box-folder 2/43)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1917 (Box-folder 2/44)
        - Barbers, 1917 (Box-folder 2/45)
        - Cooks and Waiters, 1917 (Box-folder 2/46)
        - A-Z, 1917 (Box-folder 2/47)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1917 (Box-folder 2/48)
        - K-Z, 1918 (Box-folder 2/49)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1918 (Box-folder 2/50)
        - Barbers, 1918 (Box-folder 2/51)
        - Blacksmiths, 1918 (Box-folder 2/52)
        - Boiler Makers, 1918 (Box-folder 2/53)
        - Brewery Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 2/54)
        - Carpenters, 1918 (Box-folder 3/1)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1918 (Box-folder 3/2)
        - Cereal and Flour Mill Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/3)
        - Tacoma Commercial Club and Chamber of Commerce, 1918 (Box-folder 3/4)
        - Steam and Operating Engineers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/5)
        - Electrical Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/6)
        - A-E, 1918 (Box-folder 3/7)
        - Federal Employees, 1918 (Box-folder 3/8)
        - Fire Fighters, 1918 (Box-folder 3/9)
        - Garment Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/10)
        - Hod Carriers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/11)
        - Albert Johnson, US Representative, 1918 (Box-folder 3/12)
        - Wesley L. Jones, US Senator, 1918 (Box-folder 3/13)
        - International Workers' Defense League, 1918 (Box-folder 3/14)
        - Laundry Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/15)
        - Longshoremen, 1918 (Box-folder 3/16)
        - F-L, 1918 (Box-folder 3/17)
        - Machinists, 1918 (Box-folder 3/18)
        - Meat Cutters, 1918 (Box-folder 3/19)
        - Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/20)
        - Painters, 1918 (Box-folder 3/21)
        - Plumbers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/22)
        - Puget Sound Electric Railway, 1918 (Box-folder 3/23)
        - M-P, 1918 (Box-folder 3/24)
        - Retail Clerks, 1918 (Box-folder 3/25)
        - Shipyard Laborers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/26)
        - Sheet Metal Workers, 1918 (Box-folder 3/27)
        - Street and Electric Railway Employees, 1918 (Box-folder 3/28)
        - City of Tacoma, 1918 (Box-folder 3/29)
        - Teamsters, 1918 (Box-folder 3/30)
        - Timber Workers Local No. 70, 1918 (Box-folder 3/31)
        - Typographical Union No. 170, 1918 (Box-folder 3/32)
        - U.S. Government agencies, 1918 (Box-folder 3/33)
        - U.S. Liberty Loan Committee - War Savings Committee, 1918 (Box-folder 3/34)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1918 (Box-folder 3/35)
        - Women's Union Card and Label League, 1918 (Box-folder 3/36)
        - S-Z, 1918 (Box-folder 3/37)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1919 (Box-folder 3/38)
        - Barbers Local No. 158, 1919 (Box-folder 3/39)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1919 (Box-folder 3/40)
        - A-B, 1919 (Box-folder 4/1)
        - Carpenters, 1919 (Box-folder 4/2)
        - Central Labor Council, Seattle, 1919 (Box-folder 4/3)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1919 (Box-folder 4/4)
        - Cereal and Flour Mill Workers, 1919 (Box-folder 4/5)
        - C-D, 1919 (Box-folder 4/6)
        - Electrical Workers, 1919 (Box-folder 4/7)
        - E, 1919 (Box-folder 4/8)
        - Fire Fighters, 1919 (Box-folder 4/9)
        - F-H, 1919 (Box-folder 4/10)
        - International Workers' Defense League, 1919 (Box-folder 4/11)
        - Albert Johnson, US Representative, 1919 (Box-folder 4/12)
        - Wesley L. Jones, US Senator, 1919 (Box-folder 4/13)
        - I-K, 1919 (Box-folder 4/14)
        - League to Enforce Peace, 1919 (Box-folder 4/15)
        - Longshoremen, 1919 (Box-folder 4/16)
        - Machinists, 1919 (Box-folder 4/17)
        - Meat Cutters, 1919 (Box-folder 4/18)
        - Metal Trades Council, 1919 (Box-folder 4/19)
        - Miscellaneous Trades Section, 1919 (Box-folder 4/20)
        - Municipal Employees, 1919 (Box-folder 4/21)
        - L-N, 1919 (Box-folder 4/22)
        - Painters, 1919 (Box-folder 4/23)
        - Miles Poindexter, US Senator, 1919 (Box-folder 4/24)
        - O-P, 1919 (Box-folder 4/25)
        - Railway Clerks, 1919 (Box-folder 4/26)
        - Red Cross, 1919 (Box-folder 4/27)
        - R, 1919 (Box-folder 4/28)
        - Seattle Business Women's Civic Club, 1919 (Box-folder 4/29)
        - Shipyard Laborers, 1919 (Box-folder 4/30)
        - S, 1919 (Box-folder 4/31)
        - Teamsters, 1919 (Box-folder 4/32)
        - Triple Alliance, 1919 (Box-folder 4/33)
        - Typographical Union, 1919 (Box-folder 4/34)
        - T-U, 1919 (Box-folder 4/35)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1919 (Box-folder 4/36)
        - Workers, Soldiers and Sailors Council, 1919 (Box-folder 4/37)
        - W-Z, 1919 (Box-folder 4/38)
        - A-W, 1920 (Box-folder 4/39)
        - C-W, 1921 (Box-folder 4/40)
        - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1922 (Box-folder 5/1)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1922 (Box-folder 5/2)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1922 (Box-folder 5/3)
        - A-B, 1922 (Box-folder 5/4)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1922 (Box-folder 5/5)
        - Electrical Workers, 1922 (Box-folder 5/6)
        - C-E, 1922 (Box-folder 5/7)
        - Farmer-Labor Party, 1922 (Box-folder 5/8)
        - Friends of Soviet Russia, 1922 (Box-folder 5/9)
        - Albert Johnson, US Representative, 1922 (Box-folder 5/10)
        - Wesley L. Jones, US Senator, 1922 (Box-folder 5/11)
        - F-J, 1922 (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Mine Workers, 1922 (Box-folder 5/13)
        - Musicians, 1922 (Box-folder 5/14)
        - National Labor Alliance for Trade Relations with and Recognition of Russia, 1922 (Box-folder 5/15)
        - L-N, 1922 (Box-folder 5/16)
        - P-S, 1922 (Box-folder 5/17)
        - Teamsters, 1922 (Box-folder 5/18)
        - T-U, 1922 (Box-folder 5/19)
        - Washington State Federation of Labor, 1922 (Box-folder 5/20)
        - W-Z, 1922 (Box-folder 5/21)
        - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1929-1933 (Box-folder 5/22)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1923-1927 (Box-folder 5/23)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1928 (Box-folder 5/24)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1929 (Box-folder 5/25)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 5/26)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1932 (Box-folder 5/27)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1933 (Box-folder 6/1)
        - A, 1926-1933 (Box-folder 6/2)
        - Bakery and Confectionary Workers, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 6/3)
        - Barbers, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/4)
        - Boiler Makers, 1925-1933 (Box-folder 6/5)
        - Boot and Shoe Makers, 1926-1933 (Box-folder 6/6)
        - Building Service Employees, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 6/7)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 6/8)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1930-1933 (Box-folder 6/9)
        - B, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/10)
        - Carpenters, 1929-1933 (Box-folder 6/11)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/12)
        - Central Labor Council, Seattle, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 6/13)
        - Central Labor Council, Spokane, 1928-1932 (Box-folder 6/14)
        - Centralia Liberation Committee, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 6/15)
        - Cigarmakers, 1923-1930 (Box-folder 6/16)
        - Columbia Breweries, 1933 (Box-folder 6/17)
        - Cooks and Waiters, 1923-1930 (Box-folder 6/18)
        - C, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/19)
        - Electrical Workers, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/20)
        - Operating Engineers, 1925-1933 (Box-folder 6/21)
        - Fire Fighters, 1925-1933 (Box-folder 6/22)
        - D-F, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/23)
        - Garment Workers, 1928-1933 (Box-folder 6/24)
        - Hod Carriers, 2927-1932 (Box-folder 6/25)
        - G-K, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 6/26)
        - Laundry Workers, 1924-1928 (Box-folder 6/27)
        - Longshoremen, 1925-1934 (Box-folder 6/28)
        - L, 1925-1933 (Box-folder 6/29)
        - Machinists, 1926-1930 (Box-folder 6/30)
        - Meat Cutters, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 7/1)
        - Mine Workers, 1924-1932 (Box-folder 7/2)
        - Molders, 1928-1932 (Box-folder 7/3)
        - Musicians, 1923-1928 (Box-folder 7/4)
        - M, 1924-1933 (Box-folder 7/5)
        - N-O, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Painters, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/7)
        - Plumbers, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 7/8)
        - Printers, 1926-1933 (Box-folder 7/9)
        - P, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/10)
        - Railway Carmen, 1924-1929 (Box-folder 7/11)
        - Retail Clerks, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 7/12)
        - Rex S. Roudebush, 1925-1927 (Box-folder 7/13)
        - R, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/14)
        - Sheet Metal Workers, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 7/15)
        - Stage Employees, 1925-1930 (Box-folder 7/16)
        - Stone Cutters, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 7/17)
        - Street and Electric Railway Employees, 1926-1931 (Box-folder 7/18)
        - S, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/19)
        - City of Tacoma, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/20)
        - Teamsters, 1923-1932 (Box-folder 7/21)
        - Theatrical Federation, 1926-1930 (Box-folder 7/22)
        - Triple Alliance, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 7/23)
        - Typographical Union, 1924-1932 (Box-folder 7/24)
        - T, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/25)
        - Unemployed Citizen's League, 1932 (Box-folder 7/26)
        - Upholsterers, 1928-1933 (Box-folder 7/27)
        - U, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/28)
        - Washington State, 1926-1933 (Box-folder 7/29)
        - WCFL Radio, 1928-1930 (Box-folder 7/30)
        - Women's Union Card and Label League, 1929-1933 (Box-folder 7/31)
        - W, 1923-1933 (Box-folder 7/32)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1934 (Box-folder 7/33)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1935 (Box-folder 7/34)
        - A, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 7/35)
        - Barbers, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/1)
        - Bill-Posters and Billers, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/2)
        - Brewery Workers, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/3)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/4)
        - B, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/5)
        - Carpenters, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/6)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/7)
        - C, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/8)
        - Electrical Workers, 1935 (Box-folder 8/9)
        - Federal Employees, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/10)
        - Furniture Workers, 1935 (Box-folder 8/11)
        - Garment Workers, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/12)
        - D-G, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/13)
        - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/14)
        - Longshoremen, 1934 (Box-folder 8/15)
        - Lumber and Sawmill Workers, 1935 (Box-folder 8/16)
        - H-L, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/17)
        - Meat Cutters, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/18)
        - M, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/19)
        - Sawmill and Timber Workers, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/20)
        - N-T, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/21)
        - Washington State, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/22)
        - Unidentified, 1935 (Box-folder 8/23)
        - U-Y, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 8/24)
        - American Federation of Labor, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 8/25)
        - Automobile Salesmen' Union, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 8/26)
        - A, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 8/27)
        - Bakery Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 8/28)
        - Barbers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 8/29)
        - Building Service Employees, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 8/30)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1936 (Box-folder 8/31)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1937 (Box-folder 8/32)
        - Building Trades Council, Tacoma, 1938 (Box-folder 8/33)
        - B, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/1)
        - Cannery Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/2)
        - Central Labor Councils, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/3)
        - Central Labor Council, Seattle, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/4)
        - Central Labor Council, Spokane, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/5)
        - C, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Democratic National Committee, 1936 (Box-folder 9/7)
        - Electrical Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/8)
        - Operating Engineers, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 9/9)
        - Technical Engineers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/10)
        - Furniture Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/11)
        - D-F, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/12)
        - Garage Employees, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 9/13)
        - Garment Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/14)
        - Gas Station Employees, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/15)
        - Government Employees, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/16)
        - Hotel and Restaurant Employees, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/17)
        - G-H, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/18)
        - Industrial Conference Board of Tacoma, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 9/19)
        - Inlandboatmen's Union, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/20)
        - Iron Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/21)
        - King-Ramsey-Conner Defense Committee, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 9/22)
        - I-K, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/23)
        - Longshoremen, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/24)
        - Lumber and Sawmill Workers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/25)
        - L, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/26)
        - Machinists, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/27)
        - Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 9/28)
        - Match Factory Workers, 1937 (Box-folder 9/29)
        - Meat Cutters, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/30)
        - Millmen's Union, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 9/31)
        - Molders, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/31)
        - Tom Mooney Molders' Defense Committee, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 9/32)
        - M, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 9/33)
        - Newspaper Guild, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 10/1)
        - N, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/2)
        - Office Workers, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 10/3)
        - Painters, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/4)
        - Printers, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 10/5)